Hello, everyone. Good evening. I'm XMARVELOUS DESIGNER's Xueli. Long time no see, everyone.
Today, my new colleague Hazel and I are going to explain the new features of the 2025.2 version.
This is also the first time Hazel has participated in the live broadcast.
Hazel, please say hello to everyone.
Hello, hello. I'm Hazel, a new member of the MD family.
Hazel, I'm going to explain the new features of the 2025.2 version.
Okay, everyone, please give a round of applause for Hazel.
Hazel will be the first to take over the first half of the live broadcast.
He will help the live streamers answer some questions.
Please send in your questions and participate in the live broadcast.
After the presentation, we will have a live broadcast draw.
Please join us.
See you later.
Okay.
Next, we're going to talk about some of the new features of the 2025.2 version of Marvelous Designer.
First of all, let me introduce you to some updates in our 3D window.
The first update is to convert the version into a component or configuration.
To use this feature, we need to import a virtual model first.
After downloading our virtual model,
we can use this to convert the version into a component or configuration,
because it will match our virtual model.
Okay.
In our window here, you can directly select the custom configuration function.
After selecting the custom configuration, you need to select a configuration type.
For example, we choose a hair here.
When you choose a hair, we need to enter a file,
and you will see that the original hair is automatically deleted.
Okay.
Now we need to open a file.
This file is a general 3D file format.
For example, I'm downloading an OBJ file here.
After downloading, you can see the preview of this file in the 3D window.
After that, we can select its proportion, which is its original unit.
When you change the proportion, you will see that in the 3D window,
this file will be automatically downloaded.
According to your settings, it will be downloaded.
Then you just need to adjust it to suit your needs.
When you choose the 3D model, you can choose the 3D model you want to use.
Okay.
After that, you still have some other options to set.
For example, it's a shrink chart.
For example, a shrink chart, you can manually create some shrink charts,
or use our automatically created shrink chart.
After that, you can save this file.
Okay.
After completing the registration of this configuration,
we can see that
this file is no longer an OBJ like the previous one,
but a new type of file that we have registered.
For example, the hairstyle will be put together with our virtual model.
At this time, if we go to adjust the virtual model skeleton,
for example, to change its movement,
you will see that this hairstyle will move along with our head.
Okay.
We can also use the way to reactivate the virtual model to reactivate this hairstyle,
so that it does not participate in the calculation.
Okay.
Then our configuration,
it is suitable for our virtual model to follow the virtual model.
So if you switch to other virtual models,
it can't be used directly.
Okay.
In addition to this type,
we can directly convert the clothing version into a virtual model configuration.
For example, we can select the hat version on the hat side,
and then convert it into a configuration type of hat.
Since we have already selected the version,
on the right,
you can directly see in the object window of the version,
the version we want to select will automatically be selected.
Okay.
After we have finished converting,
you can see that our conversion,
in fact, it follows the display type in your 3D window.
So if you want to convert with the thickness,
you must remember to open our display thickness settings.
If you do not open the display thickness and choose to convert,
we will see that the version converted,
it does not have the thickness of the side.
Even if I open the thickness display,
you can see that the hat part that has been converted,
it also does not have the thickness.
Okay.
Then our conversion configuration,
its physical type is a repeated physical type.
When you choose the original physical setting is repeated,
which is our repeated physical type,
you go to convert this version,
or convert our component,
it can be converted with the physical.
But if we say that we originally used a unified UV,
that is, we have already opened the UV of the UV map,
and then arrange it well,
then there is no way to automatically convert it with the texture.
Like now here,
if I choose to convert it into a hat,
because we used the UV map before,
so there is no way to bring the UV map here.
You will see that the UV map is added in a very strange form,
just as a repeated texture,
it will be added to our converted component,
or on the converted configuration.
Then in such a case,
we can choose to export this OBJ first in Marvelous Designer,
that is, for example, this hat,
we export it out.
When exporting,
select the unified UV coordinate,
then select our file here through the custom configuration,
to convert,
rather than directly select the version and convert it.
At this time,
we will use the file type,
to identify this OBJ we export out,
so that it can directly call this unified UV map.
Okay, after that,
for example,
we have already customized it into a hat,
here I have changed the model,
that is, when our virtual model's head is very large,
the hat file will also follow its head to be exported.
In addition to the hat file,
we also have some shoes files,
because the shoes are symmetrical structures,
we only need to keep one side of the shoe file.
After that,
we select all the pieces of shoes,
and here we choose to automatically convert to custom configuration.
For the configuration type,
choose shoes.
Remember to click here,
to select the direction of production,
so that it will use the world coordinates to do the world symmetry.
Okay, after symmetry,
we can take a look at this converted shoes.
In addition to being able to convert to virtual model configuration,
we can also change the version one by one,
to convert the version into a copy.
Like here,
I converted to the butterfly version of the copy,
now we can use the glue tool
to paste it on our clothing.
Because we can now copy with conflict and weight
to do some conflict simulation with the version,
so we can just stick it on here,
and then take a look at its effect.
In addition,
we can now use the copy function
to merge the multiple points on the board together.
Previously,
our glue tool was point-to-point,
and for the fake sewing,
we can merge a lot of points on the fabric on one board,
and thus achieve some one-to-multi-converting effects.
Okay,
now we can use the copy tool
to adjust the length of the sewing line,
in order to control the distance between this component and the fabric.
By adjusting the length of the sewing line,
we can better adjust
the conflict between these components and the board.
Okay,
the next one is our software model simulation.
Now,
our software model simulation can be calculated through the GPU
when it is turned on.
For example,
the band that I added here
actually has a certain pressure on the hand.
Let's reduce its frictional shrinkage a little bit,
so that its shrinkage effect is more obvious.
You will see that there will be some
shrinkage and compression effects on the wrist here.
Now,
because we have already supported the GPU simulation,
so now,
for the speed of calculation,
there is actually no big impact.
Okay,
the next one is our zipper optimization.
In the new version,
first of all,
our zipper is at the opening,
which is the position of the zipper head.
It has some optimization of the opening position.
This is the previous version.
You will see that it has some differences.
In the new version,
there is no difference between the opening position and the opening position.
In addition,
when we select all and this zipper,
that is,
the zipper is in the plate,
and then select the anti-activation,
the zipper belt will also automatically synchronize
this activation and anti-activation effect.
Okay,
now that we have a zipper on one side,
we can copy and match the modified plate
and copy this side of the zipper
to the other side of the symmetrical plate.
This can also help us save some zipper creation,
some time for these configuration creations.
In addition,
we have also added the edit zipper tool.
You can directly in the 3D window,
for example,
our zipper,
in fact,
it is cross-plated.
At the beginning,
I saw the effect started from the collar here.
Now we can directly adjust this zipper to pull to the bottom.
That is,
the zipper is created from our collar.
Okay,
let's talk about some of the settings
in the zipper attribute editor.
For example,
when we select the zipper head,
you will actually see that
it has the settings of the zipper head,
zipper,
and zipper together.
You need to select a single component again,
such as the zipper head or the zipper,
you can edit this component alone,
that is,
in our attribute editor.
If you choose the zipper bar,
you can change the adjustment of the zipper or zipper belt at the bottom of the attribute.
If we choose the zipper,
after adjusting the length here,
it will actually have a kind of zipper contraction and release adjustment effect.
For example,
if I change the length of the zipper here to be shorter than the original default setting,
it will have a kind of fold on both sides of the zipper.
In addition,
because we have an added zipper at the upper right corner of the object window,
you can use the added zipper setting to adjust it.
Our zipper will be a special type.
You can apply a unified management and adjustment to the unified type zipper.
This is the content related to the optimization of the zipper.
Okay,
next,
When we double-click a fixed pin on the board, all other fixed pins on the board will be selected at the same time.
This makes it easy for us to quickly select all the fixed pins on a board and move and adjust them at the same time.
Next is an update about Everywhere.
First of all, in Everywhere, we can now choose to switch the fixed point of binding or which boards are included in the binding.
First, we select the target point of binding.
That is, the fixed point of binding.
When we are involved in the binding process, we can choose to remove some bones.
These removed joints will not be applied to our binding.
Those red joints will not be included in the binding.
So when we do some full application of these joints, we will see that when we select these joints, they are not fully applied.
But after selecting other joints that are involved in the binding of the bones, you will see that there is a full selection.
And when we adjust, for example, in the process of posture, the costume will not change with it.
If we want to re-apply the binding of the joints, we must remember to reset the previous settings and update the binding of the joints.
Now you can see that we can re-apply these settings.
Let's say now we have re-applied the binding of these joints to Google.
If we need to re-apply the binding of these joints to Google,
we need to first use the reset button to reset the binding data.
Then we select these joints, such as the joints in the front.
After selecting them separately, select the application and bind to Google, then you will see that when we bind to Google, only these selected versions will participate in the Google binding.
If we go to modify its posture now, you can see that in fact only the front part is bound together with the virtual model.
OK, the next one is to convert to binding posture and symmetrical weight.
In fact, it is easy to understand to convert to binding posture, which is to return our virtual model from a special posture to the A pose with one click.
This way, it is more convenient for us to apply or scan some information about binding.
And here we see that its weight is not symmetrical.
This is what I manually gave to its left side.
In this case, when we do not select any joint points, we select a version first.
Then if you want to select more versions, you can press the CTRL key to select more.
Then press the right button to select the binding balance weight.
Then you can bind the weight to the other side of the matching version.
The next one is about the update of our virtual model.
Now we are supporting the use of the model of MetaHuman into Marvelous Designer using the DNA format.
OK, we now make a MetaHuman in the virtual machine.
Then remember to select the DCC setting.
After that, our MetaHuman will be divided into two DNAs as the body and the head, and then it can be integrated separately.
Then remember to set some basic settings here, such as units.
And then select the automatic generation arrangement point and Sichuan Talisman.
After we select these options, we can check in Marvelous Designer to see if our arrangement point and arrangement board and Sichuan Talisman information have been correctly imported.
After correct import, we can use these related functions to automatically test wear.
For example, some of the clothes in our material warehouse are wearing Sichuan Talisman information.
We can automatically adjust its version to MetaHuman by one click.
And the second time, we can import these clothes back to Unreal Engine, which is used in our virtual machine.
Then the next part of the update is about the update in our UV editor.
In the UV editor, we can now select all the UV cases with the same properties with one click.
For example, when we double-click a plate, we can select all the plates that are related to this plate.
Whether it is directly printed or indirectly printed, all the plates.
Then we can select UV fill.
In this way, we can fill all the plates that are related to this plate in one UV line.
In addition, we can also select the same properties.
For example, here we choose to use the same layer setting to select all the plates that are on the same layer.
Then arrange them in the same UV line.
In addition to layers, when we select the same properties, in fact, it is the same as selecting plates in the 2D window.
You can choose to use all the plates of the same plant.
Then we fill it into the same UV line through UV fill.
Finally, we can choose to use all the plates with the same particle diameter.
Fill them into a UV line.
OK.
This is the update of all the UVs that use the same properties with one click.
Next is the update of animation.
Animation update is actually a very important function in the small version update of 2025.2.
First, we have expanded the properties that can be applied to the key frame.
Now we can talk about, for example, like shrinkage and pressure.
And whether to participate in the simulation of the simulation.
Let's talk about the conversion of the format and the value of the format conversion for transformation.
Like here, we're now in a small photo of the disc.
Yes.
And when we're creating animation layers,
now we can create all the animation layers in the 3D environment at once.
It's convenient for us to go straight to the faster creation.
For example, the Verdicata or the simulation properties of the animation layers.
After that, we now can select all the verdicata at the same time.
Then the same properties of these verdicata, such as pressure, can be radiated.
Then we started to work on this.
If we choose to add a key frame for a selected layer or all layers,
it will use different settings to add key frames through our different options.
For example, we choose to add a key frame for all layers.
That is, now all the animated layers in the 3D window will be added to the key frame quickly according to our current settings.
You can add a key frame for all of these properties at once.
No matter whether it is a board or a fixed frame,
if you choose to add key frames for a selected layer,
you can only add key frames for one or more animated layers, such as these selected ones.
This is an update of our selection settings.
Now let's take a look at the pressure.
Here I am using the pressure for all the small films,
and then I will change the pressure for them.
Now I am using the pressure for the frames.
As you can see here,
because we have used the pressure for the frames,
the small frame will have an effect of inflating.
In fact, after I have used the pressure for the frames,
it is a linear change,
so it has already had pressure from the beginning when it was in the middle.
Sometimes we may have some settings
that you need to inflate it suddenly when there is no pressure at the beginning.
So we can put the pressure here at the beginning
and then the pressure here at the beginning.
The pressure is set to maintain the value.
After that, we can copy the key frame,
select all the small frames that are formed,
and cover the first key frame that we added at the beginning with the sticky key.
In this way, all the frames in the first frame are under pressure.
In this case,
if we go back to the animation,
you can see that from the position of the second key frame,
the small frame starts to inflate,
and it will inflate.
This is our pressure.
This is our pressure key frame.
Then there is another attribute of our expansion that can be used as a key frame,
which is our shrink.
For example, I want to make an animation where the sleeve becomes longer.
At the beginning, I actually shortened the sleeve,
and shrunk it with the static shrink.
After that, at the beginning,
I will add a key frame to the position where I want to start doing this animation.
After that, we will end it.
I hope that the key frame,
for example, I hope that the shrink here is set to 125,
and then I will give it a key frame at the end.
After that, we can take a look at the animation.
In the process of this linear change,
as the shrink of the film goes from the previous 30 to 125,
this sleeve will become a long sleeve from a short sleeve.
This cheongsam will become a long sleeve from a short sleeve.
And we don't actually affect the number of frames.
We just make its frame longer.
OK.
After that, it's our shape optimization.
This film, when we do a lot of movement,
or when the movement is relatively large,
it will have some impact.
In this process, we can add K-pieces to the shape optimization.
For example, we don't want some films to affect other films.
If we continue to maintain the current form,
we can add some shape optimization to it,
and then give the shape optimization K-pieces.
Then you will see that the T-shape on the inside
will not affect the outer cover.
OK.
After that, we can add K-pieces to the shape optimization.
For example, I can choose to activate the shape optimization first.
Then, in this state,
we first give the T-shape to the T-shape
that activates the shape optimization.
After that, if I want this T-shape to fall down,
I definitely want to make the line longer first,
and let it fall down little by little.
Or we can even directly anti-activate the shape optimization line afterwards,
and let this shape optimization line
automatically fall down to the ball on the hand.
OK.
Then we start recording the animation.
In the animation, we can see that
as the shape optimization is set,
it has some linear changes.
First, its length of the line increases.
Second, after we anti-activate the shape optimization,
the ball falls directly to the ground
because it has a gravity setting.
OK.
Speaking of the shape optimization,
we can K-state the weight of the shape optimization.
For example, at the beginning of the shape optimization,
we set the weight to 0 first,
so that it will not fall down
due to gravity,
and it will be pressed down to the square plate below.
Then we can increase its weight a little bit.
Just like what I set before.
Because at the beginning,
I hoped that it would not fall down,
and that it would not have linear changes.
So at the beginning,
I modified it to maintain its vertical value.
Then we let it have linear changes.
And as its weight increases,
you can see that
the rebound effect of the plate is getting worse and worse.
This is the update of some of our key real-time settings.
OK.
Next, let's take a look at some updates about AI.
First of all,
first of all,
we don't know how our personal users
can turn on the AI function.
Because AI is now default closed.
We are now going to open your account on the official website.
Then there is an AI plug-in here.
You have to click on the AI plug-in.
I agree.
This is how you can choose to open it.
After opening the AI Studio plug-in,
we can find the AI Studio inside Marvelous Designer.
This is our AI studio.
Here you can do some AI settings.
And AI uses AI to do some physics.
Yes, yes.
OK.
Next, let's take a look at the AI version editor.
The version editor is actually a fast way
to create some basic version functions.
Here we first adjust the position of the version editor for it.
Put it in the middle.
The version editor can quickly create some of our basic versions.
For example, here we have added two types of version editors.
One is the pants version.
For the pants version,
we can choose to use the flexible belt version
or the leisure version.
For the leisure version,
you will have some auditory settings,
voice settings.
OK.
Then we go to set these.
Because it is created based on your measurement value.
For example, we have some virtual models.
If its waist is very thin and the butt is very large,
we can adjust these settings separately here.
You can also choose to have more measurement data.
We can adjust it more accurately like this.
Here, when we choose a measurement data,
there will be a yellow line next to it.
The high-density line will remind you that
this is the information you want to fill in the value.
Then you can choose to add or not add.
If you choose to add,
you can set the number of measurements below.
There are also some values ​​of our measurements.
For example, you have to unlock this lock next to it,
then you can manually enter these values.
OK.
In addition, we can also adjust other versions,
such as our back pieces.
These are all used to quickly construct
a version that fits our collection,
that is, these versions of our measurement data.
OK.
In this case,
we can manually set
whether there are any additional measurements needed,
such as the height of the buttocks,
and some settings here.
OK.
In addition to these,
we can use the data to create
some versions that fit our human body
and some versions that fit our virtual model.
We can also choose to generate a skirt.
In the skirt,
there are also some,
for example,
we are a straight pencil skirt,
or a loose skirt,
to create some versions.
OK.
In the skirt,
it's actually almost the same as the pants.
We can manually create some waist,
hip,
side seam,
side seam.
In the skirt,
there are some additional attributes.
For example,
you can choose to create our skirt
according to the total length of the curve
or its straight line distance,
which is the skirt length of the skirt.
In fact,
most of the time,
you may use a little more straight line.
OK.
And you can choose the skirt version
to be left and right,
or the independent version.
And we set the whole length
or the length of the front and back pieces
separately.
You can adjust these
according to your needs.
OK.
So,
the version generator,
on the right side,
you can see that I created a skirt version
that is completely different
from the previous one.
It's because I used the AI function here.
The AI version generator,
first of all,
we still choose the settings of the skirt
as the basic setting.
Then there are some key word hints.
If you don't have any頭序,
you can click on random generation.
Then after the generation,
there will be a reference picture at the bottom.
If you think the reference picture
is the effect you want,
you can choose to click on the generation.
Then,
after clicking on the generation,
here we can,
you can,
according to the data measurement of the virtual model,
in fact,
because we are using a default virtual model,
there are already some measurement data.
You just fill in the measurement data
we choose
in this table on the right.
Chinese keywords are also OK.
OK.
Then other settings,
for example,
like the width of the butt,
if you have these settings,
you can put it,
like I am going to open the total length,
because I measured it in a whole circle.
You can fill it in.
OK.
After filling in these data,
finally,
we click on the create button,
you can see the version,
it will automatically arrange around the virtual model.
And the reference line will also be automatically created.
This is what we did just now.
According to some of the pictures we generated,
we can use the AI version to automatically generate the version,
and then we can make some adjustments to it.
For example,
there is a protruding point on its side,
we can use the reference line to round it.
OK.
The AI version generator,
in addition to using this AI function
to automatically generate a screenshot,
you can also automatically use your own,
that is,
some pre-prepared reference pictures
to make some references on the ship,
so that it can automatically generate the corresponding version.
I recommend that when you are using this function,
it is best to use it to do some simple construction.
OK.
I just replied to everyone,
this live chat is from Mr. Hazel.
Next,
we are going to the part of Mr. Hazel.
Mr. Hazel will introduce you to 2D updates
and some settings related updates.
Everyone,
applause to welcome our Mr. Hazel.
Then I will become a little Dijun.
So everyone,
don't be angry with me.
Let's start the live chat.
Hello, hello.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Dijun.
This is my first live stream in my life.
I'm a little nervous.
Today,
I'm going to introduce you to some new updates
for 2D windows.
In this update,
we added a new render tool
to 2D windows.
This tool is used to create render files.
It is very suitable for using some different versions,
such as the front of the pants.
You can see that
my pants
have already created a render file
in the top and bottom.
First of all,
I created an inner line
as a reference line for this render.
Then,
click on the render tool.
Click on this inner line I just created.
Then,
select the desired render direction.
you can see that
a render window is displayed.
At the top,
you can select the type of render.
I'm here.
I clicked on a type of render.
Then,
you can set the depth of your render.
You can set the top and bottom
to different values.
Then,
you can add a vertical value.
Vertical render.
Then,
you can set the same value
and lock it.
You can adjust the top and bottom together.
Then,
this reverse direction
can change the folding direction you just selected.
You can also adjust the angle of your fold, or you can adjust the angle of your fold more delicately.
The opposite of the previous one is the opposite of your fold to the outside or to the inside.
You can see that the sewing line here has become a foldable sewing line by pressing N directly.
When you create a foldable sewing line, the sewing line will also be generated automatically.
If we simulate it directly like this, you can see that the foldable sewing line of the waistband is very easy to pierce and cause instability.
So we usually sew it like this.
When we simulate the foldable sewing line, it is best to make a set of combinations first.
First of all, I looked at the example of the seam allowance and the thickness of the seam allowance.
We need to reduce it a little bit.
Then we reverse-sew all the sewing lines on the foldable sewing line.
After reverse-sewing, pull it out a little bit.
Use the hardening function to fold it in advance.
Let's simulate the foldable sewing line.
Then continue to make our combinations.
Turn off the hardening function.
Then activate the sewing line we just made.
After activating it, you can continue to put the foldable sewing line on the foldable sewing line.
Then press the control key to simulate.
You can see that after making this set of combinations,
the foldable sewing line at the top of the pants is not so easy to pierce.
It is arranged directly.
It is recommended that when you simulate the foldable sewing line,
it is best to arrange them in advance and organize them.
Next, I actually have a hidden shirt.
I plan to make a full-fledged decoration on the chest part of this shirt.
I have already cut out the fabric of the chest part in advance.
We will make a multi-folded creation on this chest pattern.
First of all, I have decided to set the inner line of the foldable sewing line as 10.
So I put the inner line of the foldable sewing line.
I first squeezed out an inner line and set the inner line of the foldable sewing line as 10.
Then use this inner line as the baseline line of the foldable sewing line I created.
Click on our foldable sewing tool.
Then I choose to fold to the right.
This time I plan to make a full-fledged.
Then you can see that when we raise the number to 1 or more,
the foldable sewing line below is lit.
Then I put this.
Maybe some of you are already in doubt that you haven't figured out the depth just now.
Why is there still a gap?
What is this depth and gap?
This depth is actually the part that was folded in when you created the foldable sewing line.
You can see it on the screen.
It seems that you can't see my watch.
This green part is a fold.
A section is the depth of your foldable sewing line.
The part that was folded in is the depth.
Then the pink line is the part that is in your original version.
How long is the gap to create a new foldable sewing line?
The pink part is the foldable sewing line.
Then the top is the foldable sewing line.
The bottom is the foldable sewing line.
Can you understand this way?
This is the setting of the depth and gap.
Due to the foldable sewing line,
it's relatively shallow when folding.
Okay, is it stuck?
It doesn't seem stuck.
No, it's not stuck.
So I'll change the depth to be a little bit shallow.
That's a little bit different from the width.
Here I set the depth to be 5.
And then pull it to the full.
Pulling it to the point where it can't be pulled anymore shows that this is the limit of the fold.
The limit here is 13.
And then make it full.
And then we start to play our combination again.
Pull it out a little bit.
And then select all the sewing lines on this board.
Re-activate it.
And then select this board.
Oh, we need to adjust the particle diameter a little bit.
And the conflict thickness.
And then fold it up with a folding pad.
Here you can see that the fold after folding is actually the same shape as our previous board.
It's the same.
It's just that it's inserted some fold depth into it.
So after it's completely folded up, it looks like it's going to be almost the same as our original board.
And then continue to play our combination.
Activate the sewing line.
And then arrange it a little bit.
Because our board is symmetrical on both sides,
you can just arrange it on one side and then align it on the other side.
And then I re-activated the collar that might be affected.
And then give it a simulation.
Although we can avoid a large part of the problem by playing this combination,
but because the fold here is too small,
sometimes it's still easier to have this kind of gap problem.
Here I chose to rearrange it a little bit closer.
And then simulate it.
And then try to solve this problem with a pull.
Some of them may have been placed well through a simple pull.
But sometimes it may be that you can't pull it in no matter how you pull it.
It just needs to be inserted.
At this time, we can use the selection tool.
And then select these small boards that are inserted in a bad way.
I also chose the wrong one here.
And then force it in.
And then re-activate the simulation.
It's already organized.
There's a little crack on the top.
Let's sort it out.
Insert it in.
And then simulate it.
So our board on the left is completely organized.
We can just align it on the right side.
So our board in front of the chest is already made.
Put the collar that we just re-activated.
Re-activate it again.
And then simulate it with it.
Our shirt on the front of the chest is already made.
Maybe there will be some new friends who will find out.
Why did we just only do the fold on one side of the crotch?
The crotch on the other side must have our good use.
We're going to introduce a little bit here.
A way to fix it.
Sometimes we might just want to create a fold at the top of the crotch.
But I want this fold line to fall down.
So maybe in the traditional way.
When making this kind of fold.
It's like this on the left.
Create a fold on the top and bottom first.
And then put the bottom.
Just imitate me first.
I'm going to delete the edge of the crotch below.
And then delete the sewing line.
And then.
This can create a first.
A gradually relaxing fold effect.
But when we simulate it.
We will find that the size of the pants will change.
It's traditional.
If it's a real dress.
It's a real dress.
Maybe it's like this first.
After creating the fold.
Then go back to the size of the pants.
But for some modelers.
You might think.
I didn't have too many.
The background of the clothing board.
I might be from this.
Go to the inside.
Look at the size.
Then go to our Marlboro Designer.
To extract the pattern.
And then.
And then I just want to add a small fold.
And then I have to adjust its size again.
This.
This is really difficult.
So today we have this.
A bit of a modest way.
Let you not change the size of the pants.
On the basis.
And then to create this.
A fold with a fold.
And then a fold that gradually dissipates.
This fold.
We are now starting to make this fold.
Oh, this side seems to be still.
Modifying that.
Oh, yes.
Start to do.
First of all.
We need to be on the side without the increase.
Point a straight line first.
Adjust this straight line a little bit.
Then you need to go from the waist.
That part.
Start.
Then to the end of this straight line.
We are through that.
The B-shaped fold.
To achieve this effect.
Then I continue.
Still create a worker.
Then the number is one.
Then on the side where you don't want to increase the amount.
Is the end position.
Set it to zero.
I gave a 20 at the beginning.
Then.
Now we have created a V-shaped fold.
You can see that the top is lit.
The bottom is not lit.
Because we don't need the bottom part.
So I made some cuts in the middle.
Then delete the guide line at the bottom.
Delete the inner line.
Then.
These inner lines will guide the direction of the fold.
So I.
I adjusted it a little bit here.
Adjusted these inner lines.
To better guide the direction of the fold.
Adjusted.
OK.
When I am fully satisfied with this fold adjustment.
We start to play our fold combination again.
Reduce our particle strength.
Reduce our collision thickness.
Then pull out a little.
Oh.
Um.
Did not pull out a little.
I first.
First, let's turn on the heat sink.
Then, fold it.
Fold it, fold it.
Put it a little closer.
Then, turn on the heat sink.
Okay.
Now, the heat sink has been successfully heated.
To make it look more natural,
we can delete the inner wire and simulate it a little.
You can use a short circuit to
simulate the effect you want to simulate.
Maybe in the new function video,
some friends have already seen the folding tool.
Some friends should have thought
that they can quickly create a white group in the future.
No, they can't.
In fact, this new folding tool is very useful,
but it is not very effective.
It is more suitable for the use of this kind of foldable dress that is very neat.
In fact, it is more suitable for the addition of foldable clothes on the one-piece version.
But there is an exception.
It's like this.
It's common in women's clothing or Lolita clothing.
This kind of very neat foldable dress is very neat.
This kind of drawing needs to be used as a folding tool.
If it's not this kind, it's actually more convenient to use the old way.
Here I will show you how to make this kind of repeated foldable dress.
If you need it, you can take a picture here.
The production method of the foldable dress is also below.
First of all,
I made a cut on the original version.
Then I decided that I would add a few folds.
Then the width of each fold is how much its diameter is.
Remember these two numbers.
The number of cuts and the diameter.
Now you can see that the diameter given here is 36.4.
Then we
need to delete these cuts.
Then the first point of the first-start fold must be within one-third of it.
Or at most it starts at one-third.
So you can see that it starts within this area.
Then I choose to fold to the left.
Then the number of folds.
Raise the number first.
Then fill in the diameter just set.
36.4.
And then the depth.
As long as you are in line with its settings,
you can fill it in any way you want.
The setting of the worker is that it cannot exceed one-third of the diameter.
It must be within one-third of it.
So I filled in a depth of 5 here.
Then fill in the number just set.
Then fill in as 7.
Click on confirm to create our sheet material.
Then again start another whole and whole combination command.
Habit flag of our sewing line.
Then I slightly increase the particle diameter.
In fact, this small sheet can also be raised a little higher.
I'm going to use the hardening tool to fold it a little bit,
and then re-activate the sewing line.
You can see that a group of these very light-folded,
square-folded flowers have already been created.
Then turn it over and look at the back,
you can see that its border with the other normal circle,
is actually the same.
This side is 23.2.
Then select these few lines and look at them together.
Oh, there may be a little bit of a gap.
This is because our number is the most,
it can only fill a little bit behind the number point.
So there may be some subtle gaps,
but it doesn't look bad at all.
Then,
you can delete the inner line,
and give it a little bit of a simulation,
to make it more natural.
Here,
you can adjust the particle diameter to 3,
and then re-model it again.
This kind of light-folded,
square-folded flower is done.
Then,
you can see the new setting.
This is the new setting for the new update,
the new interface setting.
You can see that we,
in this new version,
have added a new setting that can set the appearance of the lines and faces in your window.
Open the user's self-defining,
and then in the user interface,
you can see the new appearance of this column.
The upper part is the color of the lines under your various statuses,
and the lower part is the color of the lines under your various statuses.
Now,
all these colors can be self-defined.
For example,
I can adjust the inner line to purple.
After confirming it,
you will find that in the window,
whether it is a 2D window or a 3D window,
its inner line has become purple.
Then,
look down.
In addition to setting these colors,
the particle size is not actually the size of the UI.
It refers to the 2D window.
Now,
let's zoom in.
Select a line.
You can see the length of this line
and the corner of its edge.
It is the value of this line to zoom in or out.
Then,
the thickness of this column refers to the thickness of these lines around the 2D window.
Next,
we can,
well,
self-define the display settings of various statuses in our various panels.
For example,
I can change the color of the freezer to a different color.
Let's change it to a big red.
In this way,
when I go back to the 3D window,
the freezer panel will turn into a big red.
Maybe there will be some careful friends who find out
why there is a layer display setting.
When can the layer display turn green?
This is also a update of our new version.
In the old version,
if the panel has layer information,
it will only display a blue edge line in the 3D window.
But in our new version,
the panel with layer information will be displayed as grass green.
This is the same as our sister software.
Because the original display of only a blue edge line
will still make many friends forget that they have layer information.
Then,
if you keep your layer information from the beginning to the end,
it is easy to have all kinds of crossings and panel explosions.
There will be all kinds of instability.
In this way,
we have added a more clear layer setting,
which allows you to reset your layers in time.
If you regret it,
and you don't want to use these messy colors,
you can click on the bottom left corner to go back to the default settings.
Then you can go back to the default color display.
Let's go back to the default color display.
Click on the default color display.
OK.
This is the content of the new function I mentioned today.
Next,
we will enter the draw section.